[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Who is the real Steve Jobs?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "real", "Steve", "Jobs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "He's a risk taker, a gambler, charismatic, compelling.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "risk", "taker", ",", "a", "gambler", ",", "charismatic", ",", "compelling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Turner"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Can you be a genius without being all these things?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "be", "a", "genius", "without", "being", "all", "these", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "You know I used to work at this network, and I work for Ted Turner, and I think every one of those adjectives applied to him.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "used", "to", "work", "at", "this", "network", ",", "and", "I", "work", "for", "Ted", "Turner", ",", "and", "I", "think", "every", "one", "of", "those", "adjectives", "applied", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What was your reaction when he first came to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "he", "first", "came", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, you're right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "The obvious questions to me when I finished the book is did you like him?", "question_tokens": ["The", "obvious", "questions", "to", "me", "when", "I", "finished", "the", "book", "is", "did", "you", "like", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Was he likable?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "likable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "He was compelling and likable because when you first meet him, you're afraid, OK, you've heard all the tales.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "compelling", "and", "likable", "because", "when", "you", "first", "meet", "him", ",", "you", "'re", "afraid", ",", "OK", ",", "you", "'ve", "heard", "all", "the", "tales", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "You know, and salute him and all the rest of it, but likable?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "and", "salute", "him", "and", "all", "the", "rest", "of", "it", ",", "but", "likable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, you know, there are certain types of behavior you don't like.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "are", "certain", "types", "of", "behavior", "you", "do", "n't", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Is that what it was all about, you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "was", "all", "about", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I think he had an artistic sensibility.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "had", "an", "artistic", "sensibility", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "ORGAN: Didn't he even choose his own cover?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "n't", "he", "even", "choose", "his", "own", "cover", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I got chewed out -- I mean the one time I really got chewed out is because he said, I'm going to have no control over this book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "chewed", "out", "--", "I", "mean", "the", "one", "time", "I", "really", "got", "chewed", "out", "is", "because", "he", "said", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "no", "control", "over", "this", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "And he was right, you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "was", "right", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "You just said so.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "just", "said", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve", "Steve", "Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "He's the engineering genius, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "the", "engineering", "genius", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "And as Steve said he's 50 times better than any engineer that Steve has ever met, Steve Jobs has ever met.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "as", "Steve", "said", "he", "'s", "50", "times", "better", "than", "any", "engineer", "that", "Steve", "has", "ever", "met", ",", "Steve", "Jobs", "has", "ever", "met", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Did they have any type of contact at all even to the point when Steve was publicly obviously dying?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "have", "any", "type", "of", "contact", "at", "all", "even", "to", "the", "point", "when", "Steve", "was", "publicly", "obviously", "dying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Because he obviously had this huge curiosity about his real parents, but did he feel great anger, do you think, towards his father in particular?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "he", "obviously", "had", "this", "huge", "curiosity", "about", "his", "real", "parents", ",", "but", "did", "he", "feel", "great", "anger", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "towards", "his", "father", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I don't think he felt anger toward his father.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "felt", "anger", "toward", "his", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "It became a company that was global in both its brand in terms of its power, its influence, and he really did teach the world to think differently, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["It", "became", "a", "company", "that", "was", "global", "in", "both", "its", "brand", "in", "terms", "of", "its", "power", ",", "its", "influence", ",", "and", "he", "really", "did", "teach", "the", "world", "to", "think", "differently", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "The amazing thing about the iPod is here's a personal computer company.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "amazing", "thing", "about", "the", "iPod", "is", "here", "'s", "a", "personal", "computer", "company", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve", "Steve"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "How important was his wife in his life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "was", "his", "wife", "in", "his", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "You know, everything about Steve is the connection of sort of the romantic, sort of ethereal poetic side of Steve, and the realistic, smart sensible side.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "everything", "about", "Steve", "is", "the", "connection", "of", "sort", "of", "the", "romantic", ",", "sort", "of", "ethereal", "poetic", "side", "of", "Steve", ",", "and", "the", "realistic", ",", "smart", "sensible", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Yes, but, how many people have marriages like that -- that are incredibly tight, faithful, in which they really sort of fit together, both the sensible side and the poetic side?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", ",", "how", "many", "people", "have", "marriages", "like", "that", "--", "that", "are", "incredibly", "tight", ",", "faithful", ",", "in", "which", "they", "really", "sort", "of", "fit", "together", ",", "both", "the", "sensible", "side", "and", "the", "poetic", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE) that there should be (INAUDIBLE) in all this book, it shouldn't be some valedictory he's all fantastic, this should be what he's really like.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "that", "there", "should", "be", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "in", "all", "this", "book", ",", "it", "should", "n't", "be", "some", "valedictory", "he", "'s", "all", "fantastic", ",", "this", "should", "be", "what", "he", "'s", "really", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Have you had a reaction from her?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "a", "reaction", "from", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "No, I don't, I mean, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Are you surprised?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "No, no, I've -- I've been in touch.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "'ve", "--", "I", "'ve", "been", "in", "touch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "When it came to his illness, do you think he ever really appreciated that he was going to die or did he exude an air of infallibility to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "it", "came", "to", "his", "illness", ",", "do", "you", "think", "he", "ever", "really", "appreciated", "that", "he", "was", "going", "to", "die", "or", "did", "he", "exude", "an", "air", "of", "infallibility", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I think that he understood mortality even before he got cancer and there are so many people who remember him as a young man saying, you know, we all are going to die.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "understood", "mortality", "even", "before", "he", "got", "cancer", "and", "there", "are", "so", "many", "people", "who", "remember", "him", "as", "a", "young", "man", "saying", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "all", "are", "going", "to", "die", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Edison", "Ford"], "PERSON": ["Ben Franklin", "Einstein", "Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Preposterous though it seemed at the time, him to come to you and say I want the man who did the biography of Einstein to write about me, does it seem quite so preposterous today?", "question_tokens": ["Preposterous", "though", "it", "seemed", "at", "the", "time", ",", "him", "to", "come", "to", "you", "and", "say", "I", "want", "the", "man", "who", "did", "the", "biography", "of", "Einstein", "to", "write", "about", "me", ",", "does", "it", "seem", "quite", "so", "preposterous", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I'd put him in the line with Edison and Ford and certain Ben Franklin and if you're going to try to figure out what genius is, you can start with Einstein but somewhere in one of those orbits you've got to have Steve Jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "put", "him", "in", "the", "line", "with", "Edison", "and", "Ford", "and", "certain", "Ben", "Franklin", "and", "if", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "try", "to", "figure", "out", "what", "genius", "is", ",", "you", "can", "start", "with", "Einstein", "but", "somewhere", "in", "one", "of", "those", "orbits", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "have", "Steve", "Jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Einstein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Are you actually Italian?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "actually", "Italian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "I'm an Italian-American.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "an", "Italian-American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florence", "Bologna"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Do you feel Italian?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "Italian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I do in that after studying in college and kind of figuring out the restaurant business from the American's perspective, I moved to a tiny little hill town between -- between Florence and Bologna and lived there for three and a half years, which is really where I learned to speak Italian.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "in", "that", "after", "studying", "in", "college", "and", "kind", "of", "figuring", "out", "the", "restaurant", "business", "from", "the", "American", "'s", "perspective", ",", "I", "moved", "to", "a", "tiny", "little", "hill", "town", "between", "--", "between", "Florence", "and", "Bologna", "and", "lived", "there", "for", "three", "and", "a", "half", "years", ",", "which", "is", "really", "where", "I", "learned", "to", "speak", "Italian", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Are you fluent now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "fluent", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Completely.", "answer_tokens": ["Completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Come Stai?", "question_tokens": ["Come", "Stai", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Benissimo, (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["Benissimo", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stai"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$30", "$160"], "LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "$", "CD", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "How are you seeing the economy impact on those people just from what your business tells you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "seeing", "the", "economy", "impact", "on", "those", "people", "just", "from", "what", "your", "business", "tells", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, we're -- I have 19 restaurants, 9 of which are around New York City and we have everything from a pizzeria with a $30 check average to a four star Italian restaurant with $160 check average.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "--", "I", "have", "19", "restaurants", ",", "9", "of", "which", "are", "around", "New", "York", "City", "and", "we", "have", "everything", "from", "a", "pizzeria", "with", "a", "$", "30", "check", "average", "to", "a", "four", "star", "Italian", "restaurant", "with", "$", "160", "check", "average", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "If you were running the country, what would you do to fix this malaise?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "running", "the", "country", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "to", "fix", "this", "malaise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I'm -- I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "No, but what does Mrs. Batali think watching this?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "what", "does", "Mrs.", "Batali", "think", "watching", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "We had dinner last week.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "dinner", "last", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Batali"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "WP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "What do you think sometimes?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "sometimes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Life smiles upon those who smile upon life.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "smiles", "upon", "those", "who", "smile", "upon", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "As someone who has come from nothing to achieve what you have achieved, what -- what do you tell these people?", "question_tokens": ["As", "someone", "who", "has", "come", "from", "nothing", "to", "achieve", "what", "you", "have", "achieved", ",", "what", "--", "what", "do", "you", "tell", "these", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I say the best way to do it is at least 20 percent of the time try to find a way to do something for somebody else who hasn't asked you to do it because that builds your karmic account.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "the", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "is", "at", "least", "20", "percent", "of", "the", "time", "try", "to", "find", "a", "way", "to", "do", "something", "for", "somebody", "else", "who", "has", "n't", "asked", "you", "to", "do", "it", "because", "that", "builds", "your", "karmic", "account", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What's the concept of this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "concept", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, there's -- there's two kind of concepts going at the same time.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "--", "there", "'s", "two", "kind", "of", "concepts", "going", "at", "the", "same", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Spain"]}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "weight", "have", "you", "lost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I lost about 50 pounds, from the time that we worked on the Spain series, which I believe was at my biggest.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "lost", "about", "50", "pounds", ",", "from", "the", "time", "that", "we", "worked", "on", "the", "Spain", "series", ",", "which", "I", "believe", "was", "at", "my", "biggest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", ":", "NNS", ":", "RB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Was it too much paella?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "too", "much", "paella", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "There was -- yes -- too much -- too much paella and just in general too much of everything.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "--", "yes", "--", "too", "much", "--", "too", "much", "paella", "and", "just", "in", "general", "too", "much", "of", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Well, did you have a moment where you woke up and went, enough?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "did", "you", "have", "a", "moment", "where", "you", "woke", "up", "and", "went", ",", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "No, you know what, I saw the first screening of the show and I said I can't believe how big I look.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "I", "saw", "the", "first", "screening", "of", "the", "show", "and", "I", "said", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "how", "big", "I", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]